wallpaperssfree.com 2015-10-06

# Privacy Policy | Free wallpapers

## Privacy Policy

 **Privacy Policy of  www.freewallpaperss.com**  
www.freewallpaperss.com takes your privacy very seriously. We collect the user’s personal private information and details of how to use this document to our policy. Third party advertising partners, we also detail how we deal with.

 **Personally Identified Data**  
We do not recommend all visitors to the site do not give any sensitive personal information about themselves including full name, phone number, credit card, physical address, email address, or other sensitive information. We encourage minors and other users with limited decision is the ability to visit our website without the supervision of elders. freewallpaperss.com seeks to ensure that all of your personal data or offensive material must be removed immediately.

 **Server Logs**  
Like most Web sites, freewallpaperss.com web logs, database, and other server-software usage and access information. This information may include your internet protocal (IP) address, which in many cases can be translated to an affiliation (such as your work, school or internet service provider), or a geographical location. We only use this information for debugging purposes and for aggregating into anonymous usage and traffic statistics.

 **Cookies**  
While browsing freewallpaperss.com, a small number of text files referred to as “cookies” may be created on your local file system by your web browser at the request of our servers. These files allow us to personalize the browsing experience for both registered and non-registered users. You are free to delete them at any time, or configure your browser not to create them. However, we do not promise that every feature of freewallpaperss.com will function as expected without cookies enabled.

 **Third-Party Advertisers**  
In order to cover the costs of providing hd wallpapers as a free resource to the public, we have relationships with many third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by freewallpaperss.com privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date.

Google Adsense:  
We present you the following information about Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie:](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
**Sharing/Selling of Data**  
freewallpaperss.com does not share or sell personally identifiable data to third parties such as spammers or direct marketers. We respect your privacy.  
if any images appear on site are violation or copyright please inform [contact us](http://wallpaperssfree.com/contact-us/) we will remove this content from the site as soon as possible.
